A Guide to the Papers Pertaining to "Willa Cather: A Bibliography," 1965-1983
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers Pertaining to "Willa Cather: A Bibliography," 1965-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10462-c
This collection is comprised of ca. 500 items.
Joan St. Crane
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Joan St. C. Crane of the Rare Book Division, Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library, gave these materials to the Library on January 24, 1990.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of additional papers of Joan St. C. Crane of the University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginia, ca. 500 items, 1965-1983, primarily pertaining to her book Willa Cather: A Bibliography and includes correspondence with various repositories holding Willa Cather material and other Cather scholars, research files concerning various Cather works, several Willa Cather photographs, printed material pertaining to Willa Cather memorials, and miscellany.
Contents List
- Acknowledgements 1965-1980 (Box 1)
- Alexander's Bridge 1979 (Box 1)
- April Twilights 1978 (Box 1)
- Cather Collections 1978-1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence re Willa Cather 1971-1983, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Correspondence with Alfred A. Knopf 1976-1982 (Box 1)
- Correspondence with William A. Koshland 1976-1981 (Box 1)
- Correspondence with Bernice Slote, Virginia Faulkner, and the Center for Plains Studies 1976-1980 (Box 1)
- Death Comes for the Archbishop 1976-1979 (Box 1)
- Ephemera 1973-1980 (Box 1)
- Expenses 1979 (Box 1)
- Foreign Editions 1977-1979 (Box 1)
- Houghton Library - Harvard University 1978-1979 (Box 1)
- Houghton Mifflin Company - Copyrights and Permissions 1977-1980 (Box 2)
- A Lost Lady n.d. (Box 2)
- McClure Autobiography 1977-1978 (Box 2)
- My Antonia 1979 (Box 2)
- Photographs and Oddments 1977-1981 (Box 2)
- Printed Material 1973-1982 (Box 2)
- Reprints 1977 (Box 2)
- Shadows on the Rock 1976 (Box 2)
- The Song of the Lark 1979 (Box 2)
- Style ca. 1968 (Box 2)
- University of Nebraska Press 1977-1979 (Box 2)
- University of Texas Knopf Archive 1976-1979 (Box 2)
- Unpublished Cather Material/the Will of Willa Cather 1977-1978 (Box 2)
- Willa Cather Pioneer Memorial 1979-1980 (Box 2)